+977-980-522-7303

CARRER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working Computer Engineering Major currently attending Tribhuvan University (I.O.E), with 3+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of web design and programming skills to successfully fill the role at your company. Frequently praised as focused by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

EXPERIENCE

Upwork, Kathmandu, Bagmati Freelancer, Jun 2019 – Present

• I get to work in variants of projects. Rather than learning a categorical types of projects, I get to learn and experience different kinds of projects in different languages and frameworks. Upwork helped me to improve my communication skills and taught me how to showcase my skills to the client, it genuinely edified me on the side a client wants me in.

Fiverr, Kathmandu, Bagmati Freelancer, Sep 2019 – Present

• This was a great platform for me to showcase what I am capable of as a computer engineer. Fiverr has contributed lots to amend my communication skills and it taught me how to represent my accommodations to clients, how would they love to see my services through the gigs feature provided by Fiverr.

Blend Group of Companies

Data Science Instructor and Developer, Sep 2020 – Present

• Blend helped me to build myself as a team member and exposer of myself to the corporate world. The only things I missed were teamwork and exposer to the corporate world. Blend was a good source for me to achieve these qualities.

EDUCATION

Global Collegiate School Pokhara, Gandaki High School Diploma (+2) (2016)

Relevant Coursework: Science

Tribhuvan University (I.O.E) Lalitpur, Bagmati

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E) Computer Engineering Candidate (Expected Graduation 2020)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Web Development

- Django/Flask
- JavaScript
- CSS
- Html
- Bootstrap

Software Development

- Python
- C
- C++

REFERENCES

Jilani S (FOUNDER (DIRECTOR) BLEND GROUP OF COMPANIES)

sameer@blendinfotech.com

<u>Akhila B</u> (MANAGING PARTNER(BLEND INFOTECH))

akhila@blendinfotech.com